gfmag.com 2018-12-27

# Privacy and Cookie Policy | Global Finance Magazine

We at Global Finance Media Inc. (“Global Finance,” “we” or “our”) consider our clients’ privacy to be a top priority, and as such we have developed this Privacy Policy.  This Policy outlines how we fulfill our legal responsibilities under applicable data privacy and protection laws, and details what information we collect on the Global Finance Media website [www.GFMag.com](http://www.gfmag.com/) (the “Site”), how and for what purposes it is collected and processed, and the steps we take to secure this information. 

This Privacy Policy is provided by Global Finance Media, Inc., a Delaware corporation. Our primary business address is 7 E. 20th St., New York, NY 10003 (“we” or “us”). Our employee identification number is: 13–3872642.

Please take the time to read this Privacy Policy, along with our Terms of Use, both of which contain important information about the way in which we process personal data.

This policy explains our privacy practices and covers the following:

  * Information Collected
  * How We Use This Information
  * Cookie Policy
  * Information Sharing and Disclosure
  * Cross-Border Data Transfers
  * Information Security
  * Information Retention
  * Your Privacy Rights
  * To Opt-Out of Third Party Information Collection
  * Dispute Resolution
  * Third Party Sites
  * Children’s Privacy
  * Changes in this Privacy Policy
  * Applicable Law
  * Contact Us

**Information Collected**

_Information You Provide Directly to Global Finance._  In order to benefit from services from the Site, you may need to provide us with information about yourself, including: your name, postal address, email address, telephone number, name of your employer or company, title, and your month of birth.  Services for which you would volunteer your personal information may include: subscribing to the  _Global Finance_  magazine through the Site, registering with the Site or participating in a survey on the Site.

_Information We Collect Automatically._  In addition to information you choose to provide to us, we also use standard Internet technologies to collect automatically certain additional information, including information for purposes of registering with the Site and information about your use of the Site, such as:

  * **IP Address.**  When you come to our Site, we collect your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, which identifies the computer or service provider that you use to access the Site. We may use IP addresses to collect information regarding the frequency with which specific visitors visit various parts of our Site. We may combine this information with personally identifiable information that we have collected to make our Site and our communications to you more targeted to your interests.
  * **Cookies.**  Our Site also uses cookies. Cookies are small text files that are stored on a user’s computer and allow websites to remember information about users. The Site stores a corresponding file (same ID tag) to the one the cookies set in your brows[er and in this](http://sdf.com/) file they can track and keep information on your movements within the site and any information you may have voluntarily given while visiting the website, such as email address.
  * **Web Beacons and Other Technologies.**  The Site uses other tracking tools, including web beacons. Web beacons are images on the Site (or in emails that the Site sends to you) that help us determine what parts of the Site you have visited, whether you have opened an email that we have sent to you, or otherwise to measure the effectiveness of the Site. These technical methods may involve storing data in a browser on a device so that when used in "local storage" mode, your browser may enable data to be stored across sessions. These technical methods may also involve the transmission of information directly to us or to a service provider authorized by us to collect information on our behalf. See [here](http://www.nielsen-online.com/privacy.jsp?section=leg_scs) (Nielsen) and [here](https://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html) (Google Analytics) for more information about how we use third party services to collect and use information on this Site. 
  * **Device Information.**  We may collect [device-specific information](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/example/device-specific-information.html) (such as your hardware model, operating system version) to ensure the correct operation of the Site on your device as well providing relevant advertising.

The information we collect automatically may be combined with information that is personally identifiable so that we can make our Site and communications more interesting to you as further described in this Privacy Policy.

_Third-Party Online Advertising._  Some of the advertisements you see on this Site and other websites are delivered by third parties who also collect information through cookies, web beacons, and other technologies about your online activities on this and other websites, in an effort to understand your interests and deliver to you advertisements that are tailored to your interests. These third parties also may use information about your usage of the Site and features within the Site, to target and serve advertisements to you and to analyze the delivery of advertisements on the Site.

Third parties that currently serve ads on our Site, and thereby may collect information about your online activities to deliver tailored ads, such as [DoubleClick](https://www.doubleclickbygoogle.com/) and [Quantcast](https://www.quantcast.com/). These companies may offer you a way to choose not to have your information used for advertising purposes. For more information on opt-out options, see “Your Privacy Rights" below.

_Third Parties Information Providers._  Our subscriptions services sometimes use additional information from third party brokers, researchers, or other agents (who have gathered this information lawfully) to help us contact you or help us make marketing or other business decisions.  These third parties may give us access to your personal information, if you have allowed them to do so.

****How We Use This Information****

_Global Finance_  may use information that it collects through the Site about you for some or all of the following business purposes:

  * to administer the Site; maintain and manage your account, deliver subscription or other services that you have requested, and enhance your experience on our Site;
  * to process and track your service orders and provide the services you request;
  * to communicate with you about the Site or other products or services in which you may be interested, or to respond to your inquiries or comments;
  * to perform business analyses or for other purposes to improve the quality of our business, the Site, and the products and services we offer; or
  * in any other manner in accordance with your consent.

If you choose to provide us with your e-mail address, your postal address and/or your telephone number, you may receive periodic communications from  _Global Finance_  with information about new products, services or upcoming events.  For information on how to opt not to receive these communications, see "Your Privacy Rights,” below.

We are committed not to process your information collected in a way incompatible with these purposes. However we may also use your information for unanticipated purposes not disclosed in this Privacy Policy.  If so, we assure you that these uses will always be highly respectful of your privacy concerns and will be subject to the ethical standards of this Privacy Policy.

**Cookie Policy**

We use cookies for a variety of purposes in order to enhance the quality of our Site. We use “session cookies” to provide continuity from page to page. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. We also use persistent cookies. Persistent cookies allow parts of our Site to recognize your browser when you return after your first visit to that part of our Site. Cookies allow us to personalize your return visits to our Site and to save you time during certain activities.

_Global Finance_  enables you to opt out of cookies that are not required to enable core site functionality by clicking here, but does not process any other Do Not Track signals. Please remember that if you delete your cookies, or use a different browser or computer, you will need to set your cookies preferences again.

Most web browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable existing cookies. You can find out how to do this for your particular browser by clicking "help" on your browser's menu or by visiting [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) or [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to take full advantage of all our site features.

The table below explains the cookies we use and why and how long they last.

Provider

| 

Name(s)

| 

Expires

| 

Purpose  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
Google Analytics

| 

_ga

| 

2 years

| 

This cookie name is associated with Google Universal Analytics - which is a significant update to Google's more commonly used analytics service. The new service reduces the reliance on cookies in general, and only sets this one, although Google also say data can be collected without setting any cookies. This cookie is used to distinguishes unique users by assigning a randomly generated number as a client identifier. It is included in each page request in a site and used to calculate visitor, session and campaign data for the sites analytics reports.  
  
DoubleClick for Publishers

| 

__gads

| 

2 years

| 

This cookie is associated with the DoubleClick for Publishers service from Google. Its purpose is to do with the showing of adverts on the site, for which the owner may earn some revenue.  
  
Quantcast

| 

__qca

| 

2 years

| 

This is a cookie usually associated with Quantcast, a digital advertising company. They provide website rankings, and the data they collect is also used for audience segmentation and targeted advertising.  
  
Google Analytics

| 

__utma

| 

2 years

| 

Used to distinguish users and sessions. The cookie is created when the javascript library executes and no existing __utma cookies exists. The cookie is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics.  
  
Google Analytics

| 

__utmz

| 

2 years

| 

Stores the traffic source or campaign that explains how the user reached your site. The cookie is created when the javascript library executes and is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics.  
  
Global Finance Magazine

| 

csfrtoken

| 

n/a

| 

This cookie is associated with the Django web development platform for Python. It is designed to help protect a site against at particular type of software attack on web forms.  
  
Global Finance Magazine

| 

cookies_notification_accepted

| 

n/a

| 

Used to indicate if the user has accepted GFMag's cookie policy.  
  
Global Finance Magazine

| 

django_language

| 

n/a

| 

Used to indicate the currently selected language in Global Finance Site.  
  
Global Finance Magazine

| 

exp_expiration

| 

n/a

| 

Used by GFMag.com to track users free access to articles.  
  
Global Finance Magazine

| 

exp_last_activity

| 

n/a

| 

Used by GFMag.com to track users free access to articles.  
  
Global Finance Magazine

| 

exp_last_visit

| 

n/a

| 

Used by GFMag.com to track users free access to articles.  
  
Global Finance Magazine

| 

interstitial_modal_viewed

| 

24 hours

| 

Used by GFMag.com to track viewing of interstitial advertisements.  
  
Global Finance Magazine

| 

sessionid

| 

n/a

| 

A unique identifier for the user used to identify the user on the Global Finance Magazine web servers.  
  
**Information Sharing and Disclosure  **

We take very seriously our responsibility to maintain your privacy with respect to your information. We will therefore share that information only with the following entities, and only under these circumstances:

  * with entities that provide services on our behalf, including Site development, maintenance and support, email distribution, and promotions management, only to the extent that these entities need the information to perform their services or as required by law, unless any additional use or sharing of the information is separately permitted under another provision of this Privacy Policy;  
within the Class Editori Group;
  * with identified entities whose products or services you specifically use or request to receive while you use the Site;
  * with other selected third parties which we believe provide products or services our clients may find interesting or appealing so that they may send you promotional materials about goods and services that they offer, but from which you have the opportunity to opt out of our sharing personally identifiable information about you as described below in “Your Privacy Rights";
  * when we believe that doing so is required by law, may be necessary to protect any person’s property, rights, or safety, or to investigate a potential violation of law, will help to enforce any terms of use or other legal agreement, or will help resolve disputes that arise in the ordinary course of business, or in the event of a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale;
  * in aggregated or other non-personally identifiable form; or
  * in accordance with your consent.                         

We are very selective when determining whether a third party organization is worthy of being entrusted with our clients’ personal information, and we hold those organizations with which we do share such information to high security and ethical standards as well as an obligation to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**Cross-Border Data Transfers  **

Information that  _Global Finance_  collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which _  Global Finance _operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy, as well as with all applicable regulations.  You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

**Information Security  **

We at  _Global Finance_  recognize that you value your privacy and that when you provide us with your personal information, you place your trust and confidence in us.  To that end, we have implemented reasonable technical and organizational precaution at our physical facilities to safeguard any personally identifiable information that you provide to us and to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. However, no method of transmitting or storing electronic data is ever completely secure, and therefore we cannot warrant or guarantee that such information will never be accessed, used or released in a manner that is inconsistent with this policy.

**Information Retention**

_Global Finance_ will keep your information stored on our systems in accordance with this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.  Unless otherwise indicated, we will store your information for as long as it takes to provide our services to you, or until you request its deletion. _Global Finance_  may also delete this information in the context of maintaining its customer base, for example when you terminate your subscription or registration.  _Global Finance_  may keep your data for longer than our stated retention period if we cannot delete it for legal, regulatory or technical reasons. If we do retain information in such a manner, we will not store your information for longer than is reasonably necessary or required by law, and we will continue to ensure that appropriate safeguards are in place to protect your privacy.  In the case that Global Finance has engaged third parties to provide services on our behalf, that data will stored on their systems only for as long as is necessary for us to provide services to you. 

**Your Privacy Rights **

We understand the importance of protecting our customers’ privacy, and we therefore provide you with the opportunity to access, review, or rectify the information we collect as well as to opt-out of having your personally identifiable information used or disclosed for certain purposes. You may also request that such information be deleted.

_To Contact Us about Information Collected.  _

For all purposes of this Privacy Policy, such as: 

  * questions, comments or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, or reports of possible violations of this Policy;
  * if you wish to opt out of receiving promotional communications from  _Global Finance_ , or request that we not share personally identifiable information about you with third parties for the third parties’ marketing purposes;
  * if your personal information changes, or if you believe that  _Global Finance’s_ records have inaccurately recorded your personal information;
  * if you would like to change your preferences relating to your  _Global Finance_  magazine subscription;
  * if you would like to withdraw or modify consent for us to process your personal data on the basis you provided for when you submitted your personal data to us.

Questions, comments and requests regarding this Policy should be addressed to:

_Global Finance  _  
Attn: Richard Scholtz Managing Director, EMEA  
St. Mary Abchurch House  
123 Cannon Street  
London EC 4, UK  
Telephone: +44 20 7 929 0777  
E-mail: [ gfmail@gfmag.com](mailto:gfmail@gfmag.com)

Alternatively, you can contact us through the “[Contact Us](https://www.gfmag.com/contact-us/)” section of our website.

Because we plan our communications in advance, it may take several weeks for your request to become effective. If you continue to receive our communications in error after expressing an opt-out preference, please let us know so that we can investigate and rectify the situation.

**To Opt-Out of Third Party Information Collection  **

Third parties that currently serve ads on our Site may offer you a way to choose not to have your information used for advertising purposes:

  * To access Double Click’s privacy policy, click [ here](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). To opt-out of data collection by Double Click, see [ here](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/html/opt-out.html).

  * To access Quantcast’s privacy policy, click [ here](https://www.quantcast.com/how-we-do-it/consumer-choice/privacy-policy/). To opt out of data collection by Quantcast, see [ here](https://www.quantcast.com/company/opt-out/).

  * To access Nielsen’s privacy policy, click [ here](http://www.nielsen-online.com/privacy.jsp?section=leg_scs).  To opt out of data collection by Nielsen, see [ here](http://www.nielsen.com/content/corporate/policy/en/cookie-policy.html).

  * To access Google Analytics’ privacy policy, click [ here](https://support.google.com/analytics/topic/2919631?hl=en&ref_topic=1008008). To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites by using the Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-On, see [ here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

These and other third-party companies may also be members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of receiving tailored ads from member companies. To opt out or to obtain information about the technologies member companies use or their own privacy policies, please visit the NAI consumer opt out page. Also, through the Digital Advertising Alliance, several media and marketing associations have developed an industry self-regulatory program to give consumers a better understanding of and greater control over ads that are customized based on their online behavior across different websites. To make choices about interest-based ads from participating third parties, please visit the DAA consumer opt out page.

**Dispute Resolution**

If you have any complaints regarding our compliance with this Privacy Policy, please contact us. We will investigate and attempt to resolve complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure of personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Third-Party Sites  **

If you click on or interact with a hyperlink or advertisement that you find on the Site, you may leave our Site or send information to a different website. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to your interactions with other websites, even if you find a link to them on our Site, and so you should read the privacy policy of the third-party website provider to see how your personally identifiable information will be treated on its site.

**Children’s Privacy**

Our Site is a general audience site, and we do not knowingly collect information about children under 16 years old through the Site. If we learn that we have collected personally identifiable information from a child under 16 other than in a manner authorized by law, we will delete that information from our database.

**Changes in this Privacy Policy**

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the most recent version of the Policy on the Site, along with an indication of the date on which the Policy was amended most recently. If we make any material changes in the way we collect, use, and/or share personally identifiable information that we collect about you through the Site, we will notify you by sending you an email at the last email address that you provided us and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on the Site. In order to assist us with this, you should notify us of any changes to your personal information, by contacting us as set out below. In any event, changes to this Privacy Policy may affect our use of personally identifiable information that you provided us prior to our notification to you of the changes.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

**Applicable Law**

This Privacy Policy shall be governed by the laws of the State of New York (excluding conflicts of laws rules).

**Contact Us**

If you have questions or wish to send us comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

_Global Finance_  
Attn: Richard Scholtz Managing Director, EMEA  
St. Mary Abchurch House  
123 Cannon Street  
London EC 4, UK  
Telephone: +44 20 7 929 0777  
E-mail: [ gfmail@gfmag.com ](mailto:gfmail@gfmag.com)

These terms were last updated on May 24, 2018.
